We've looked at the node interface and the element interface,
لقد تناولنا واجهة العقدة وواجهة العنصر،
but there are just so many more interfaces.
ومع ذلك يوجد العديد من الواجهات.
Just think about the anchor element or a heading element,
فكِّروا في عنصر الارتساء أو عنصر العنوان،
each one of these is backed by its own interface with properties and methods.
حيث يتم دعم كل من هذه بواجهته الخاصة ذات الخصائص والأساليب.
To see a list of all of these interfaces,
لرؤية قائمة تتضمن جميع هذه الواجهات،
let's check out the web APIs page.
دعونا نطلع على صفحة واجهات برمجة تطبيقات الويب.
Now, we can scroll down a little bit over here and in the N category, we'll find node.
الآن، يمكننا التمرير لأسفل قليلًا هنا وفي الفئة النهائية، سنعثر على عقدة.
And we can scroll down a bit more and on
ويمكننا التمرير لأسفل أكثر وأكثر
the left-hand side of page we can find the element interface.
وفي جانب الصفحة الأيسر يمكننا العثور على واجهة العنصر.
Let's take a look at this interface up here.
دعونا نلقِ نظرة على الواجهة المتوفرة هنا.
Where is HTML? Here we go.
ما المقصود بلغة HTML؟ ها نحن ذا.
HTML element, let's look at this interface.
عنصر HTML، لنلقِ نظرة على هذه الواجهة.
Now, in this interface we can see that it inherits from element,
الآن، يمكننا أن نرى في هذه الواجهة أنها سترث من العنصر،
which inherits from node.
الذي يرث من العقدة.
So every single HTML element will inherit these properties and methods.
لذا فإن كل عنصر HTML وحيد سيرث من هذه الخصائص والأساليب.
And this HTML element interface has its own properties and methods.
وتشتمل واجهة عنصر HTML هذه على خصائصها وأساليبها الخاصة.
Now going back to the list of all of them,
ونعود الآن إلى القائمة التي تتضمنها كلها،
let's look at something specific like the anchor element right here.
لننظر إلى شيء محدد مثل عنصر الارتساء المتوفر هنا.
So the anchor element inherits from the HTML element.
ويرث عنصر الارتساء من عنصر HTML.
Going back, let's see is there a video?
ها نحن نعود، دعونا نرى إذا كان يوجد فيديو؟
There's got to be an HTML video tag.
لا بد من وجود علامة فيديو HTML.
Let's scroll to the bottom here.
لنقم بالتمرير إلى الأسفل هنا.
And here's HTML video element interface.
ويوجد هنا واجهة عنصر فيديو HTML.
And this inherits from HTML media element,
هذه ترث من عنصر وسائط HTML،
which inherits from the HTML element,
والذي يرث من عنصر HTML،
which inherits from element and node.
والذي يرث من العنصر والعقدة.
And this HTML video element interface gives us
وتقوم واجهة عنصر فيديو HTML هذه
the properties and methods for every single video tag.
بإعطائنا الخصائص والأساليب لكل علامة فيديو واحدة.
So there are really a ton of
لذا يوجد بالفعل عدد كبير من
different interfaces with a lot of different properties and methods.
الواجهات المختلفة بخصائص وأساليب مختلفة.
So, you should definitely check out this page.
لذلك، يجب أن تتأكدوا من الاطلاع على هذه الصفحة.